

DETAILS

afanadorjuanita@gmail.com

github.com/JuanitaAK

in linkedin.com/in/juanitaak

06 10 01 74 51

SKILLS

- JavaScript, PHP,
 Python, Swift, SQL,
 HTML, CSS, Git
- Teamwork
- Organizational skills
- Autonomous
- Creative
- Rigorous

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

2022-2024

Ada Tech School Paris

MASTER COMMUNICATION

2012

Université Paris 8 Saint - Denis

LICENCE CINEMA

2008

Université Paris 1. Sorbonne-Panthéon

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- French Bilingual
- English Bilingual

HOBBIES

New technologies, Cinema, TV shows, Cycling, Puzzles

Juanita Afanador Kowalski

Looking for an apprenticeship in Web / Mobile development - Full Stack- March 2023

PROFILE

After several years of experience in the restaurant and retail industries, I am currently reorienting myself to become a web developer. I am currently studying in a programming school and I am looking for a company where I can do a 12-month apprenticeship. My career path has allowed me to develop my adaptation, communication and perseverance skills. I like to take on challenges, learn constantly and use my problem-solving skills. I look forward to applying my technical knowledge in a challenging and positive working environment.

IT CREATIONS - AVAILABLE ON GITHUB

APP FOR SURFERS - "SURF SPOTS"

iOS App. OOP programming in Swift, Python, Flask and Xcode. API call. Use of Git, GitHub.

PLATFORME OF MICROBLOGGING - "MEME WORLD"

Back-end and Front-End microblogging platform. OOP programming, MVC pattern in PHP and MySQL. Laravel framework. Use of Git, GitHub and Docker. Pair programming and project management.

ONLINE TO-DO LIST - "ONE DAY TODO"

Online Todo list. Individual project. Programming in JavaScript and CSS with React. Creation and use of props, states and keys, to pass data from user from different components. Use of Git and GitHub,

E-COMMERCE WEBSITE - "OLD FURNITURE FOR A NEW LIFE"

Back-end and Front-End E-Commerce website. Programming in JS with React-Bootstrap, Node.js, Express, MongoDB. API creation. Use of Git, GitHub and Miroo. Teamwork, pair and mob-programming.

SOCIAL NETWORK - "MATCH N SET"

Social network for sport lovers. Programming in PHP, HTML, CSS, MySQL Workbench, MAMP, Git and GitHub. Teamwork, pair-programming and project management.

BROWSER EXTENSION - "ON AIR TODAY"

Chrome extension featuring the television schedule of the day in the United States. Programming in JavaScript, HTML, CSS. Use of an API, use of Git and GitHub. Teamwork, pair-programming and project management.

DATA VISUALIZATION - INTERACTIVE WEATHER SITE

Weather forecast visualization website by geolocation or by entering the location name. Programming in JavaScript, HTML, CSS. Use of two APIs. Use of Git and GitHub. Team work and project management.

VIDEO GAME -"MICHONNE'S ZOMBELAD"

In a post-apocalyptic world, the player must escape from a mob of zombies. Programming in LUA language on the Pico-8 software. Worked on event-driven programming. Teamwork, pair-programming and project management.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

BEAUTY DEPARTMENT MANAGER

2013 - 2022

Sephora

Général Leclerc 2021 - 3M€ / La Canopée 2020 - 9M€ / Gare Montparnasse 2018 - 3M€ / La Défense 2013 - 30M€

- $\bullet\,$ Store management. Lead, coach, and train teams of 13 to 75 people.
- Guarantor of the customer experience: team planning and motivation. Inventory management, coordinating and monitoring the store's expenses and finance management.
- Monitoring and relaying business indicators of the Sephora teams
- Coordinate and monitor the evolution of KPIs with sales representatives of multiple brands. Analyzing results to create action plans
- Leading of team meetings and team building workshops

RESTAURANT MANAGER

2008 - 2013

McDonald's Levallois-Perret,

- Leading teams of 10 to 30 people. Team planning and management.
- Responsible for the restaurant general operations. Equipment quality check and finance.
- Creation of a training plan for all McDonald's employees.
- Career development of both team members and other managers.